How did this happen?
What happened!
It's all because of you!
What?
Don't come to my house again!
MOON SUNG-HYUN
KIM SHI-KYUNG
HYUN-SUK
HWANG HYE-JIN, CHA JUN-HYUK,
CHOI JI-HYE, LEE HYO-BIN
KIM KYUNG-MIN, KI HYUN-WOO,
KIM WON-HOON, LEE CHANG-HO
THE CHAIRMAN IS LEVEL 9
Places, characters, institutions
and events in this drama are fictitious.
Please...
Why you don't understand?
The owner of this building
has changed.
Therefore, it is okay to clean it all up.
Mom!
Sir, we can negotiate this.
If you do this to us, how can we...
This is none of my business.
If you're that curious,
why don't you call the owner?
I will try my best to explain it to him.
- If you tell me his number...
- Maybe it's someone you know well?
What?
Na Yi-soo...
You didn't know that?
You didn't know.
Hey, she didn't know.
Isn't he the heir of Big Picture?
We would like to inform you that
Chairman Na Jun has been elected...
...as the new chairman of
Big Picture, a school corporation,...
...with more than half members
agreeing to the election.
Wait!
I am against the election.
And I am asking you
for re-appointment.
What are you doing now?
You expect me to do nothing?
I am the current chairman
of Big Picture, a school corporation,...
...Na Yi-soo.
What? That kid is the chairman?
Please be quiet.
Then, this vote is one vote short
of a majority.
So we postpone the voting.
The voting will be held
at Balhae High School.
Hey, isn't it great
that the nutritionist is back...
...and our old school lunch is back?
So, Yi-soo was behind that
Marine camp meals for us.
Let's call him Voldemort.
Just call him Na-Yi-soo,
not Voldemort.
Then, Yi-soo can't go back to school?
Everyone would hate it if they found out
a high school student was the chairman.
Ba-tang!
If you want to apologize, that's fine.
We can't believe anything
we say between us anyway.
I know it may sound like an excuse,
but there is nothing I can do.
I did that because I was so scared.
I did that so Se-ra wouldn't
bother me anymore.
I thought we were on a same boat...
...but you still believe that
everything can be solved with lies?
A YEAR AGO
Hello!
Hi!
Then, have you been to Africa?
It would be faster to find a place
I've never been to.
Wow, I'm jealous.
I still don't have a passport.
Really?
Are you Son Eun-bin?
Let go of me.
You don't have to lie to me.
I have nothing to say, so let it go.
What were you ashamed of
so you lied to me?
How will you survive here for three years
as a student from lower class?
Still, I thought you had
no malicious intent to me.
I never thought you would
do this to me again.
I don't care if you hate me!
But don’t hate Yi-soo.
Because he didn't do anything wrong.
The school foundation
is having a hard time now.
They say it will be difficult
to give free tuition...
...for the students who
receive social assistance.
How can this happen so suddenly?
I will try to find a way for you.
Isn’t it senseless for me
to endure this much?
Ba-tang. It's not like that...
Thank you for all this time.
I have said this.
Yi-soo is the chairman.
So what?
It's only a matter of time before
President Na-Jun becomes the chairman.
Master...
We don't have much time
until the vote.
So are you going to sit there
doing nothing?
Does everyone say that I am too young
and unsuitable to be the chairman?
Moreover, I have gone around
threatening to destroy the school.
It would be a good chance
for reappointment.
You've been singing about
refunds and exchanges.
But now you really want
Balhae High School.
Yes.
Now I truly want to become one.
The chairman.
It helped me learn
a lot of things I didn't know.
It's about time.
Wait a moment.
When your father decided that
you would become the chairman...
...he asked me to give you this gift.
Mom...
Today, my one and only son...
...wants me to make
his favorite tteokbokki.
Because a mother
can't just sit by and watch.
- Are you filming it good?
- Yes.
What's happening?
The brake isn't working...
Perhaps that was the last message
that your father left.
Did you have a nice dream?
I feel refreshed because I slept so well.
Glad to hear that.
From now on, you will need
to get some sleep.
AGENDA FOR CHAIRMAN'S DISMISSAL
Everyone!
School is a place that
responsible for a person's life.
Can you leave a place like that
in the hand of 18-year-old chairman?
A guy like him?
No matter how much the world has changed,
running a school is still a business.
Leave it to a management expert
to stop the big spending...
...by the foundation which is
causing problems for us.
Right. What a good speech.
AGENDA FOR CHAIRMAN'S DISMISSAL
I know that many people are worried...
...to entrust this school
to an 18-year-old.
So maybe that's why...
...my father wanted me to be graduated
from high school as the requirement.
Yes.
I am still an immature
and inadequate person.
A lot of things happened while I was
running the school for several months.
Because of my ambition,
I got ruined here and there.
As you said...
...school is a place that responsible
for a person's life.
So where did you learn
that at schools...
...the rich have privilege,
and the poor don't have anything?
The chairman is the person
who responsible for management.
That's right.
But at the same time...
...we are also educators who must
develop good character in our students.
We know that business
at school is important.
We also know that a school's reputation
is determined by the grades.
But is it true that schools
only exist for business?
At school, we spend a lot of time
with our friends...
...and sometimes we fight.
I think we can share our daily lives
and even experiences...
...and many emotions from society.
I won't say that I'm a great educator.
Even a guy like me
who only got 9th grade...
...was able to avoid failing with the help
from my friends and teacher.
I think Balhae High School is a place...
...where less fortunate students…
…can work hard and get first place.
It doesn't matter if I am dismissed
as chairman of the board.
But...
...I hope these aspects of
Balhae High School are maintained.
AGENDA FOR CHAIRMAN'S DISMISSAL
Good morning.
I worked as a contract teacher
at Balhae High School before...
...and recently became a full-time
teacher, my name is Baek Jo-hee.
I...
After received
President Na-jun's suggestion...
...I made a wrong decision.
Teacher Yoo didn't do his job so well.
Teacher Baek, this is your last year?
Yes. My contract
will be expired this year.
Do teachers move to another school
if they are unable to secure...
...a full-time contract after
completing their two-year contract?
Yes. Perhaps it should be that way.
So, we just do like this.
What kind...
The Chairman told me...
...to ignore everything that happened
to Teacher Yoo that day.
In return, I received the position
of full-time teacher.
How can it be....
Where did they learn
all this strange stuff?
Do you think you could solve
everything by lying?
I asked her to do that.
Do you think she's lying now?
This vote is meaningless. It's been
five minutes since this started.
Do I have to deal with this nonsense?
I lost both of my parents!
They both died
in separate car accidents.
This is something that rarely
happened to other people.
Why did it only happen to me twice?
The day before
my father passed away...
...and the day before
my mother passed away...
...you've switched the cars
that have just been inspected, right?
So?
And so I think I should tell them
about you used the school foundation...
...to raise a slush fund.
Do you have any proof?
From now on, I will speak as a lawyer.
- Attorney Hwang...
- What's going on?
What's going on?
Oh, my God, what is that?
What is that?
This is a case data that has been hidden
due to suspicion of additional crimes.
If this information had been known
to the world earlier...
...maybe, instead of Chairman Na-seong...
...Na Yi-soo would be the target.
We ask the dismissal of Na Jun,
Vice President of Big Picture...
…on charges of conspiracy to commit
murder and creating a slush fund!
Stop it, you bastard!
I am no longer speaking as a lawyer
for Big Picture...
...but as a lawyer for Na Yi-soo.
Hey, what are you doing?
Stop it.
Oh God, do something.
- Principal!
- Teacher, please!
Oh my God!
I told you to stop them!
If this keeps up, he'll...
COURT ISSUES ARREST WARRANT FOR
CHAIRMAN NA-JUN OF BIG PICTURE.
Welcome back.
Chairman, you already came?
Isn’t it moist?
Thanks to you, I got sponsored
this time. It's for you.
Hey, is that something that
all students have?
Hey...
...you're not happy that I’m back?
Now is not the time for that.
I am the chairman.
If you fail again, your chairmanship
will be canceled.
Finally, I returned to school.
Terrible morning school time.
Although a miserable time awaits me
in the classroom...
What is it called?
Be the best!
Na Yi-soo, don't look.
Okay, after that...
...in Korean expressions...
This is the precious time
that I will miss someday.
Are you not doing your job properly?
What else is wrong with you today?
When it comes to schools, shouldn’t
everyone able to enjoy education equally?
Some people carry books in their bags,
while others carry them in pads.
So, do you want to give
each person one pad?
Yes.
You're going to use it
as a YouTube machine anyway.
For me, YouTube is both
a teacher and a friend!
A teacher and a friend...
It's not convincing enough.
Seriously, as soon as I graduate,
I'm going to fire you first.
Are you threatening me now?
Whether it’s level 1 or level 9...
I like myself the way I am, right now.